<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:background="#00688B"
    android:layout_height="fill_parent"
    android:weightSum="0">
   
   
    <LinearLayout android:id="@+id/linearLayouttrans" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/image"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_weight="0.08"
            android:scaleType="fitStart"
            android:src="@drawable/img" >

		</ImageView>
    </LinearLayout>
    <TabHost 
    android:id="@+id/tabhostTrans"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:layout_height="fill_parent">
    <LinearLayout
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="fill_parent"
        android:padding="5dp">
        <HorizontalScrollView  android:id="@+id/horizontalScrollView1" 
        android:fillViewport="true"
        android:scrollbars="none"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <LinearLayout android:id="@+id/linearLayout2" android:orientation="horizontal" android:layout_height="fill_parent" android:layout_width="fill_parent">
        <TabWidget
        
            android:id="@android:id/tabs"
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content" 
            />
            </LinearLayout>
    </HorizontalScrollView>
        <FrameLayout
            android:id="@android:id/tabcontent"
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="fill_parent"
            android:padding="5dp" >
            
            <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_phase1" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView3" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_phase1" android:gravity="center">
                        <TextView android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:text="PROBLEM STATEMENT\nThe Objective of Phase I is to design and build a manual robot which picks up weights from ground and places them in the specified positions in the Arena in the alloted time. \n\nCOMPETITION RULES\nThe Objective is to move all the ten blocks from Zone A to Zone C within the stipulated time . The teams securing maximum points shall be declared as the winners in the Phase 1, all those teams moving at least three blocks within the stipulated time will qualify to Phase2. The Time limit for Phase I will be 10 minutes.\nAt the beginning of the game, the teams will have to place their machines in the Start Zone (in Zone A) marked red .\nEach team will be given an initial time of 2 minutes to set up their machine in the arena.\nIf the block is dropped by the manual machine anywhere in the arena , the block and the machine will be put back to their initial positions and the game will not be paused.\nThe Machine should not, under any circumstance, cross the white line separating Zone B and Zone C .\nIn case of any technical problem with the machine, it can be resolved and should be placed back to the starting zone, Zone A with the current block placed in its initial position . The game won\'t be paused (the timer will be running). The organizers should be acknowledged before such an action.\nPoints at the end of the stipulated time will be calculated as:\nScore = 500 - (Time taken in seconds) + (No. of blocks transported to Platform 3) * 100 + (No. of blocks transported to Platform 2) * 200 + (No. of blocks transported to Platform 1) * 300.\nThe Machines should not leave their respective arenas at any point of time during the game. No part of the machine should touch anything outside the arena during the course of the game.\nThe Machine cannot cause any damage to the block or any part of the arena during the course of the game. If found doing so it will lead to disqualification of the team. Judges hold the right to subjectively evaluate this clause.\n\n\nARENA SPECIFICATION" android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textView2" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
                        <ImageView android:id="@+id/imageView1" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:src="@drawable/transporter7" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></ImageView>
                        <TextView android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:text="The arena consists of three zones, made from plywood.\nZONE A\nZone A is the pickup point of the blocks. The starting zone for the manual machine will be marked. The outer dimensions of Zone A are 1.2m * 0.7m (length * breadth). The blocks shall be placed randomly in Zone A. Zone A will be separated from Zone B by a boundary wall of height 0.07m.\nZONE B\nIt mainly consists of a bridge with a slope of width 40 cm, and base length 25cm. The height at the maximum elevation of the slope is 10cm, the top portion of the bridge is an elevated platform of dimensions 0.4m * 0.35m. The entire zone has a size of 1.20m * 0.80m, refer to the sample arena.\nZONE C\nThis is the zone meant to unload the weights; it is at ground level and separated from zone B by a white line. The dimension of the zone is 1.20m x 0.95m. In Zone C there will be three Collection pits for the wooden blocks, with 0.4m * 0.2m area on top and height of 20cm (platform no1), 15cm (plarform no2) and 10cm (platform no3) respectively. The top of the collection pits will have a boundary wall of height 1cm ." android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textView3" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
                    </LinearLayout>
                </ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>

                       <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_phase2" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView3" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_phase2" android:gravity="center">
                        <TextView android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:text="PROBLEM STATEMENT\nThe objective of Phase II is to design and construct an autonomous and a manual machine pair ; where the manual machine picks up blocks from the ground and hands them over to the autonomous one, which dumps the blocks in a pit, within a stipulated period of time. \n\nCOMPETITION RULES\nThe goal of the game is to put all the blocks into the pits in minimum possible time. The teams with the maximum points will be declared winners. The teams will be given a maximum of 10 minutes to finish the task.\nAt the beginning of the game, the Team will have to place their manual machine in the Start Zone (in Zone A) marked red and their autonomous machine in the Start Zone (in Zone C).\nThe manual machine has to hand over the blocks to the autonomous machine, and while doing so, the autonomous machine has to lie completely in its Start Zone in Zone C .There is no stipulation on the number of blocks that can be transported by the autonomous machine in one run. The manual machine should not place the blocks directly in the pit.\nThe teams will be given an initial time of 3 minutes in the arena for calibration of their sensors. Note that this time is not included in the 10 minutes of the competition. Therefore, a total of 13 minutes (including 3 minutes initial time) will be given for each team.\nThe blocks should be dumped in the pits by the autonomous machine.\nOnce a block is picked by the manual machine, if it is dropped anywhere in the arena before handing it over to the autonomous machine, the block will be placed back in Zone A and the Manual Machine will have to start from the starting zone in Zone A. In case the Autonomous Machine drops the block on the runway, it will lead to a restart (Clause 10), and the dropped block will be placed back in Zone A.\nIn case of any technical difficulty faced by manual machine it can be resolved and should be placed back in the starting zone in zone A with the current block placed in its initial position, the game won\'t be paused( the timer will be running), the organizers should be acknowledged before such an action.\nPoint system : At the end of the stipulated time the points will be calculated using the following formula:\nPoints = 600 - (time taken in seconds) + (No of blocks in correct pit ) * 200\nOnly blocks dropped by the autonomous machine into the pits will be counted for calculating the score.\nRestart:In case of any technical difficulty on the part of the team, the autonomous machine can be repositioned to the starting zone in Zone C by one of the team members. Only three restarts are allowed per team. The handling time is also included in the total match time and no extra time will be given. The machine will be unloaded of any blocks that it is carrying in this case. The block will be replaced in Zone A by the same team member. The organizers have to be informed in advance before doing the same and the game will not be paused.\nThe Machines should not leave their respective arenas at any point of time during the game. No part of the machine should touch anything outside the arena during the course of the game.\nThe Team Members are not allowed to enter the arena at any point of time during the game (except for the case explained in Clause 10).\nThe Machine cannot cause any damage to the block or any part of the arena during the course of the game. If found doing so it will lead to disqualification of the team. Judges hold the right to subjectively evaluate this clause.\nARENA SPECIFICATION\nManual Zone\nZONE A\nZone A is at the ground level and would be made from plywood. The starting zone for the manual machine will be marked. The outer dimensions of Zone A are 1.20m x 0.70m (length x breadth). The blocks shall be placed randomly in Zone A. Zone A will be separated from Zone B by a boundary wall of height 0.07m.\nZONE B\nIt consists of an ascending slope of width 40 cm, and base length 25cm.The height at the maximum elevation of the slope is 10cm . The landing of the slope is an elevated platform of dimensions 0.4m x 0.35m . Zone A and Zone B are the same as in phase I.\nAUTONOMOUS ZONE\nZONE C\nZone C has an outer dimension of 1.20m x 1.20m. The floor of Zone C is black in colour (painted with non-gloss black paint) and has a grid of 0.03 m wide white lines on it, in order to aid the navigation of the autonomous machine. The regions where white line becomes discontinuous are meant to stop the autonomous machine, so that it can pick or drop the blocks in the pit. The discontinuities are only in straight regions of the path." android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textView2" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
                       </LinearLayout>
                </ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>
            
            
            <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearTransIntro" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
                <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView1" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTransIntro" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                        <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/text_transporter_title" android:text ="Transporter" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_gravity="center"  android:gravity="center"  android:textSize="20dp" android:layout_weight="0.03"></TextView>
                        <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textRoboTransIntro" android:text="Human Beings are one of the laziest class of living species . And it is this laziness that led to a vast number of inventions and discoveries, Starting from wheels and now pausing at Robots. Robots reduces human efforts . Here in Transporter , we use these Tech Monsters to carry objects to some specified destination . \n\n\'Transporter\' made its first appearance at Tathva\'06 . This time it is going bigger and bigger with two phases in competition, one for manual machines alone and other a combined version of manual and autonomous machine. To make the competition much more exciting each phase carries its own prize. To take part in the second phase the contestant must qualify in the first phase, or may choose to compete only in the first phase. " android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
                    </LinearLayout>
                </ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>
            
            
            <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTransRules" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
               <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView2" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_rules" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                        
                <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textView2" android:text="The teams must adhere to the spirit of healthy competition. The Teams must not damage the opponent\'s machine in any way.\nA Team can have a maximum of 4 members. Inter-college teams are permitted.\nThe machine would be checked for its safety before the event and would be discarded if found unsafe for other participants and spectators.\nAny team that is not ready at the specified time will be disqualified from the competition.\nThe name of your machines must be prominently displayed on them.\nJudges\' decisions shall be treated as final and binding on all. Judges reserve the right to disqualify any team indulging in misbehaviour.\nThe organizers reserve all rights to change any or all of the above rules as and when required. Changes in rules, if any will be highlighted on the website and notified to the registered participants."
 android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
 					</LinearLayout>
 					</ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>
            
            
              <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_fab" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
               <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView3" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_spec" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                        
                <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textView2" android:text="ROBOT FABRICATION\nBase of the machine must not be greater than 0.35 m x 0.25 m x 0.5 m. Boundary of the base is defined by the points on the machine touching the ground in the horizontal position. The machine should fit into a box, not to exceed the above constraints.\nThe dimension constraints mentioned above are only for the machine and are not applicable for the external wired/wireless remote control used to control the machine manually or the power supply ( if the machine uses an external placed power supply ).\nDuring the game, the machine can expand or detach itself into multiple parts provided it does not damage the arena in any way. The judges hold the right to subjectively determine if the machine violates this clause.\nMachines cannot be constructed using readymade Lego kits or any readymade mechanism but use of readymade gear assemblies is allowed. Violating this clause will lead to disqualification of the machines. Judges hold the right to subjectively evaluate this clause.\n\nROBOT PROPULSION\nThe Machine can use an externally placed or on-board electric or non-electric power supply. Use of compressors is not allowed. However the power supply must be non-polluting and must satisfy the safety constraints determined by the judges. In case the machine is using a non-electric power supply, kindly get it approved from the organizers beforehand via email. Organizers are not responsible for inconvenience if approval is not sought.\nThe method of propulsion is at the discretion of the builder, provided it does not damage the arena in any way and it satisfies the safety constraints determined by the judges. The judges hold the right to subjectively determine if the machine violates this clause.\nIn case of an electric power supply, the voltage at any point on the machine must be lower than or equal to 12V throughout the game.\nThe organizers will provide a standard 12V, 1A DC power supply.Any extension cords, eliminators, adaptors etc. required should be arranged by the participants themselves.\n\nROBOT CONTROLS\nThe Machine has to be necessarily controlled by some wired/wireless remote control mechanism at all stages of the game.\nIn case of wired mechanism, the wire must be slack at any point of time during the game.\nThe total length of wire extending from the remote control to the machine must be minimum of 3 meters.\nIf the Machine is using a external wireless remote control , make sure that it has sufficient range and that it can control the machine well without any lag .\n\n\nDIMENSION AND FABRICATION\nThe Machine must fit within a box of dimensions 0.25 m x 0.15 m x 0.25 m (Length x Breadth x Height) at the beginning of the game.\nThe Machine should be completely autonomous, self contained and should not communicate with any external agency in any manner.\nThe autonomous machine is not allowed to dismember itself or leave parts on the arena.\n\nPOWER SUPPLY AND PROPULSION\nThe machine must use power converted from a source of electrical energy. Commercial batteries like dry cells and lead acid cells are permitted. Chemicals, compressed gas and combustion power methods are strictly prohibited.\nThe machine must have an onboard source of power. External source of power is not allowed.\n"
 android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
 					</LinearLayout>
 					</ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>
            
            <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTransContact" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
                <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textRoboTransContact" android:text="SANANTHU R KRISHNAN\nEvent Manager\nPhone:+919400590976\nE-mail:transporter@tathva.org\n\nK PRATYUSHA REDDY\nEvent Manager\nPhone:+918089833707\nE-mail:transporter@tathva.org\n\nARUN TONY\nEvent Manager\nPhone:+918714164835\nE-mail:transporter@tathva.org"
 android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
            </LinearLayout>
         	    <LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTransPrizes" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
                <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textRoboTransPrizes" android:text="\tPhase I\nFirst\tRs. 8000/-\nSecond\tRs. 5000/-\nThird\tRs. 3000/-\n\n\tPhase2\nFirst\tRs. 12000/-\nSecond\tRs. 8000/-\nThird\tRs. 4000/-"
 android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
            </LinearLayout>
         	<LinearLayout android:layout_width="match_parent" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTransBlockSpec" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:orientation="vertical">
             <ScrollView android:id="@+id/scrollView3" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
                    <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@+id/linearRoboTrans_spec" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
                     
                <TextView android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium" android:id="@+id/textRoboTransBlockSpec" android:text="There will be 10 cylindrical blocks, each having a base diameter of 4 cm and height 8 cm, and an approximate weight of 150 gm (within 10% error). Blocks are made using wood. All blocks will have a metallic semi-circular ring (of non-magnetic material) on the top." 
                android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content"></TextView>
                </LinearLayout>
                </ScrollView>
            </LinearLayout>
            
            
          </FrameLayout>
            
    </LinearLayout>
    
</TabHost>
 </LinearLayout>